Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Clemson, 1979 January 10
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1979 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1396)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1979 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1397)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1979 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1398)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1979 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1399)
  - North Carolina, 1979 January 13
    Duke loss; score: 68-74
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1979 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1400)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1979 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 45, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1401)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1979 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 46, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1402)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1979 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 46, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1403)
  - Wake Forest, 1979 January 18
    Duke win; score: 81-69
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1979 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1404)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1979 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1405)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1979 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1406)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 47, 1979 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1407)
  - NC State, 1979 January 21
    Duke win; score: 75-69
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1979 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1408)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1979 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1409)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1979 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1410)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1979 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1411)
  - Virginia, 1979 January 24
    Duke win; score: 84-66
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1979 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1412)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1979 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1413)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1979 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1414)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1979 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1415)
  - Wake Forest, 1979 January 31
    Duke win; score: 75-60
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1979 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 46, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1416)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1979 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 46, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1417)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1979 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 46, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1418)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1979 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1419)
  - Maryland, 1979 February 03
    Duke win; score: 87-78
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1979 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1420)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1979 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1421)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1979 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1422)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1979 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 47, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1423)
  - Virginia, 1979 February 06
    Duke win; score: 64-63
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1979 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1424)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1979 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1425)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1979 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1426)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1979 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1427)
  - Pittsburgh, 1979 February 10
    Duke loss; score: 69-71
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 1, 1979 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1428)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 2, 1979 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1429)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 3, 1979 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1430)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 4, 1979 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1431)
  - NC State, 1979 February 14
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1979 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1432)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1979 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1433)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1979 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1434)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1979 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1435)
  - Maryland, 1979 February 16
    Duke loss; score: 68-70
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1979 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1436)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1979 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1437)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1979 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1438)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1979 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1439)
  - Louisville, 1979 February 18
    Duke win; score: 88-72
    - Duke vs. Louisville: Reel 1, 1979 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1440)
    - Duke vs. Louisville: Reel 2, 1979 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1441)
    - Duke vs. Louisville: Reel 3, 1979 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 48, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1442)
  - Clemson, 1979 February 21
    Duke loss; score: 49-70
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1979 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1443)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1979 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1444)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1979 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1445)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1979 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1446)
  - North Carolina, 1979 February 24
    Duke win; score: 47-40
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1979 February 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1447)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1979 February 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1448)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1979 February 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1449)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game film coverage, 1979 February 24; DVD
  - Wake Forest, 1979 March 01
    Duke win; score: 58-56; NCAA Tournament, Raleigh, NC
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1979 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1450)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1979 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1451)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1979 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1452)
  - NC State, 1979 March 02
    Duke win; score: 62-59; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1979 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1453)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1979 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1454)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1979 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1455)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1979 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1456)
  - North Carolina, 1979 March 03
    Duke loss; score: 63-71; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1979 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1457)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1979 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1458)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1979 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1459)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1979 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1460)
  - St. John's, 1979 March 11
    Duke loss; score: 78-80; NCAA Tournament, Raleigh, NC
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 1, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1461)
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 2, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1462)
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 3, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1463)
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 4, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1464)
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 5, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1465)
    - Duke vs. St. John's: Reel 6, 1979 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 49, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1466)
  - Kentucky, 1979 November 17
    Duke win; score: 82-76; Tip Off Classic, Springfield, Mass.
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 1, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1467)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 2, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1468)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 3, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1469)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 4, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1470)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 5, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1471)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 6, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1472)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Unidentified game film coverage, 1979 November 17; DVD
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Unidentified game film coverage, 1979 November 17; DVD
  - Wake Forest, 1979 November 30
    Duke win; score: 72-70; Big Four Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1979 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1473)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1979 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1474)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1979 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1475)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1979 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1476)
  - North Carolina, 1979 December 01
    Duke win; score: 86-74; Big Four Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1979 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1477)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1979 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1478)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1979 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1479)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1979 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1480)
  - Princeton, 1979 December 05
    Duke win; score: 81-45
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1979 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1481)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1979 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1482)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 3, 1979 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1483)
  - East Carolina, 1979 December 08
    Duke win; score: 92-73
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1979 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1484)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1979 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1485)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1979 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1486)
  - Pennsylvania, 1979 December 11
    Duke win; score: 70-57
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 1, 1979 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1487)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 2, 1979 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1488)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 3, 1979 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1489)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 4, 1979 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1490)
  - Boston College, 1979 December 21
    Duke win; score: 70-64; Industrial National Classic, Providence, RI; Reel 3 missing
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 1, 1979 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1491)
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 2, 1979 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1492)
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 4, 1979 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1493)
  - Providence, 1979 December 22
    Duke win; score: 82-78; Industrial National Classic, Providence, RI
    - Duke vs. Providence: Reel 1, 1979 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1494)
    - Duke vs. Providence: Reel 2, 1979 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1495)
    - Duke vs. Providence: Reel 3, 1979 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1496)
  - Vermont, 1979 December 28
    Duke win; score: 92-67; Iron Duke Classic
    - Duke vs. Vermont: Reel 1, 1979 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1497)
    - Duke vs. Vermont: Reel 2, 1979 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1498)
    - Duke vs. Vermont: Reel 3, 1979 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1499)
  - Cincinnati, 1979 December 29
    Duke win; score: 87-75; Iron Duke Classic
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 1, 1979 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1500)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 2, 1979 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1501)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 3, 1979 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1502)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 4, 1979 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1503)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Unidentified game film coverage, 1979 December 29; DVD
  - Colgate, 1980 January 05
    Duke win; score: 73-44
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Reel 1, 1980 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1504)
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Reel 2, 1980 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1505)
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Reel 3, 1980 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1506)
  - Georgia Tech, 1980 January 07
    Duke win; score: 55-42
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1980 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1507)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1980 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1508)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1980 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1509)
  - Clemson, 1980 January 09
    Duke loss; score: 82-87
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1980 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1510)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1980 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1511)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1980 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1512)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1980 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1513)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Unidentified game film coverage, 1980 January 09; DVD
  - North Carolina, 1980 January 12
    Duke loss; score: 67-82
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1980 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1514)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1980 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1515)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1980 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1516)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1980 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1517)
  - Wake Forest, 1980 January 16
    Duke win; score: 67-66
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1980 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1518)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1980 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1519)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1980 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1520)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1980 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1521)
  - NC State, 1980 January 19
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1980 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1522)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1980 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1523)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1980 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1524)
  - Georgia Tech, 1980 January 21
    Duke win; score: 56-49
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1980 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1525)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1980 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1526)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1980 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1527)
  - Virginia, 1980 January 23
    Duke loss; score: 84-90
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1980 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1528)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1980 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1529)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1980 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1530)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1980 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1531)
  - Pittsburgh, 1980 January 26
    Duke win; score: 82-61
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 1, 1980 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1532)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 2, 1980 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1533)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 3, 1980 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1534)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 4, 1980 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1535)
  - Wake Forest, 1980 January 30
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1980 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1536)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1980 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1537)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1980 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1538)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1980 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1539)
  - Maryland, 1980 February 02
    Duke loss; score: 82-101
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1980 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1540)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1980 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1541)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1980 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1542)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1980 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1543)
  - Virginia, 1980 February 06
    Duke loss; score: 69-73
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1980 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1544)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1980 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1545)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1980 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1546)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1980 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1547)
  - Marquette, 1980 February 10
    Duke loss; score: 77-80
    - Duke vs. Marquette: Reel 1, 1980 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1548)
    - Duke vs. Marquette: Reel 2, 1980 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1549)
    - Duke vs. Marquette: Reel 3, 1980 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1550)
    - Duke vs. Marquette: Reel 4, 1980 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1551)
  - NC State, 1980 February 13
    Duke loss; score: 59-76
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1980 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1552)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1980 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1553)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1980 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1554)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1980 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1555)
  - Maryland, 1980 February 16
    Duke win; score: 66-61
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1980 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1556)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1980 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1557)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1980 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1558)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1980 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1559)
  - Clemson, 1980 February 20
    Duke win; score: 87-82; Reels 1 and 2 missing
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1980 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1560)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1980 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1561)
  - North Carolina, 1980 February 23
    Duke loss; score: 71-96
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1980 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1562)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1980 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1563)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1980 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1564)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1980 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1565)
  - NC State, 1980 February 28
    Duke win; score: 68-62; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1980 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1566)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1980 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1567)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1980 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1568)
  - North Carolina, 1980 February 29
    Duke win; score: 75-61; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
  - Maryland, 1980 March 01
    Duke win; score: 73-72; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1980 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1573)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1980 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1574)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1980 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1575)
  - Pennsylvania, 1980 March 08
    Duke win; score: 52-42; NCAA Tournament, West Lafayette, Ind.
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 1, 1980 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1576)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 2, 1980 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1577)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 3, 1980 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1578)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Reel 4, 1980 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1579)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Unidentified game film coverage, 1980 March 08; DVD